Guide to the Don Edward Fehrenbacher Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional Material
  - The Chicago Democrat and the sectional crisis, 1854-1961. Fehrenbacher's Master's Thesis, University of Chicago., 1948 (Box 1)
Craven, Avery 1962, 1963, 1965
Degler, Carl N. 1963
Fleming, Donald 1966
Frankenstein, Alfred 1957
Fredman, Lionel E. 1958
Graebner, Norman 1959, 1960, 1961, 1963, 1966
Hutchinson, William T. 1957, 1958, 1961, 1962, 1969, 1970
Knoles, George H. 1968, 1972
Littell, C. F. (Judge) 1958, 1961, 1962, 1965
Lyman, Richard 1968
McDonald, Forrest 1957, 1958
Pomeroy, Earl 1969, 1970, 1971, 1972
Potter, David 1962, 1963, 1966, 1968, 1969, 1970
Sharp, William F. 1965
Weisberger, Bernard 1957, 1958, 1959, 1960, 1962, 1965, 1968, 1970